[
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Barnabas_Brimstone_Background",
        "PlayerPrompt": "“What’s happened?”",
        "NPCResponse": "An old enemy has returned and amasses his forces. The citizens have fled, fearing invasion is imminent. \\n\\nNow the Praetorians keep order in our streets and on our roads, but their skirmishes with these foes have depleted their ranks.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_1625_0201_ImhotepTalkTo_A",
        "PlayerPrompt": "“If you’re Imhotep, I’m looking for you.”",
        "NPCResponse": "Then this is a fortuitous day for us both for I am he! \\n\\nThere’s a sandy monstrosity that seems to have a way to release these unusual bonds. But I doubt it’ll simply hand it over.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_1625_0201_ImhotepTalkTo_B",
        "PlayerPrompt": "“Yes, she's headed to New Corsica.”",
        "NPCResponse": "Remarkable woman! A brilliant mind for one so young. \\n\\nBut we mustn’t waste any time. Something evil stirs in the sands. I’ll meet you both in New Corsica. There’s much to do!",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_1625_0103_AbanTalkTo",
        "PlayerPrompt": "“Easy… Are you Aban?”",
        "NPCResponse": "My master Imhotep… gone to New Rhacotis… I was to collect Ghazi… meet him there… \\n\\nI didn’t see them… didn’t hear them…",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_1624_0301_GhaziTalkTo",
        "PlayerPrompt": "“How's his mind holding up?”",
        "NPCResponse": "It appears stable… for now. But I will watch him closely. \\n\\nSomething's still amiss. And my instincts are rarely wrong, remember? It can happen but it's as rare as an eclipse.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_1624_0302_ImhotepTalkTo_A",
        "PlayerPrompt": "“Is this Ancient magic?”",
        "NPCResponse": "It is indeed. A sorcery taught to me by one of the Ancients themselves. My mentor. \\n\\nIt isn’t what we thought, by the way. The Ancients. They were not gods. Though they wielded power as if they were.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_1624_0302_GhaziPreRitual",
        "PlayerPrompt": "“I'm not easily rattled.”",
        "NPCResponse": "Yes, I noticed. You're as solid as the firmament. \\n\\nAnd I thank Isis for that.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_1624_0302_GhaziPostRitual",
        "PlayerPrompt": "“What’s going on, Ghazi?”",
        "NPCResponse": "Imhotep's mind has shifted. The gentle soul of the Great Sage is gone. \\n\\nAnother has arisen in his place…",
        "AchievementUnlock": "16_Topic_RitualComplete",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_1624_0303_GhaziPostRitual2",
        "PlayerPrompt": "“I won't let him down.”",
        "NPCResponse": "I know the vault the Great Pharaoh speaks of, but I've never ventured there myself. \\n\\nIt’s a cursed place filled with dark secrets and the specters of a violent past.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "16_Topic_RitualComplete",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_1624_0401_GhaziTalkTo",
        "PlayerPrompt": "“How’s Imhotep holding up?”",
        "NPCResponse": "Honestly, I’m worried. I’ve made more elixir, which helps to control his affliction. \\n\\nI fear Imhotep's formula is not strong enough. I could potentially devise a new one but my alchemy skills are not the equal of his.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_1625_0701_ImhotepTalkTo",
        "PlayerPrompt": "“Here, drink this!”",
        "NPCResponse": "*cough* Ah, thank the Powers it’s you. Please forgive me. I was not myself. \\n\\nRa’s Light, this elixir is most potent. And tastes wonderfully of cinnamon. Well done!",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_1625_0801_ImhotepTalkTo",
        "PlayerPrompt": "“You doubted your Sword?”",
        "NPCResponse": "I was cautiously optimistic. And you are not my sword, you are the Sword of Brimstone Sands! \\n\\nPlease return to New Corsica. Ghazi will be worried sick and will be delighted to see you.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_1625_0801_GhaziTalkTo",
        "PlayerPrompt": "“You’ll make me blush.”",
        "NPCResponse": "The flush of color would suit you. \\n\\nI knew you would do it. My instincts are never wrong, remember?",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_1624_0901_ImhotepTalkTo",
        "PlayerPrompt": "“Fancy clothes?”",
        "NPCResponse": "Robes of state. This is the raiment of a noble ruler from a great land. \\n\\nThere is so much history in these threads and these jewels.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_1624_0902_EvandrusTalkTo",
        "PlayerPrompt": "“Maybe I can help with that.”",
        "NPCResponse": "I would welcome any help, my friend! \\n\\nI was trained in weapons, tactics, and military strategy. But I’m afraid I have little experience with politics and governing.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_1625_Coro_GhaziTalkTo",
        "PlayerPrompt": "“They’re all behind you, Your Highness.”",
        "NPCResponse": "Very well, then. I will accept this great honor from the people. \\n\\nThank you for being so stubborn-- uhm, I mean, for your guidance and wisdom.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "Topic_1624_Coro_ImhotepTalkTo",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What will you do now?\"",
        "NPCResponse": "I shall return to the library. There are still matters that require investigation. \\n\\nAs for you, be sure to celebrate this moment with appropriate wild abandon. If you overdo it, come see me for some herbal remedies.",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": ""
    }
]
